针孔相机的一个问题是它们创建的图像非常非常
One problem with pinhole cameras, is that the images that they create are very, very
昏暗，这是他们如此难以捕捉的原因之一和原因
dim and that's one of the reasons that they are so hard to capture and the reason that
如果我们看到从特定点出现的所有光线，图像是暗淡的，
the images are dim, is if we look at all the light rays that emerge from a particular point,
在这个例子中，只有一条光线通过并形成图像，其余的
in this example, only one of those light rays goes through and forms the image, the rest
光线射到不透明的平面上，被吸收或反射到其他地方。
of the light rays hit the opaque plane and are absorbed or reflected off to somewhere else.
因此，如果我们想让我们的图像更亮，我们需要能够利用更多的光
So if we want to make our image brighter we need to be able to utilize more of the light
离开物体的光线和我们这样做的方式是使用镜头。
rays that are leaving the object and the way we do that, is to use a lens.
镜头是一种非常简单的技术，用于收集更多留下特定光线的光线
A lens is a very simple technique for gathering more of the light rays that leave a particular
指向世界。我们再次使用我们的图形示例，我们可以看到光线离开
point in the world. Again we have our graphical example and we can see the light rays leaving
一个特殊的点，他们都通过镜头并击中图像平面。所以在这里
one particular point, they've all passed through the lens and strike the image plane. So here
我们捕获了许多更多的光线，因此我们形成的图像会更亮。
we've captured many, many more light rays, so the image that we form will be brighter.
我们可以更正式地描述一下。我们考虑远离镜头的距离
We can describe this a bit more formally. We consider the distance away from the lens
我们称之为距离F的平面和距离的镜头直径
plane which we will call the distance F and the diameter of the lens which is the distance
Phi和我们可以创建一个数字，通常被称为镜头的F数，其中
Phi and we can create a number, which is generally referred to as the F-number of the lens, which
是F与Phi的比率。镜片的F值通常刻在正面
is the ratio of F to Phi. The F-number of the lens is typically inscribed on the front
镜头;在这种情况下，它是一个F1.4镜头，这意味着资本F等于1.4。越小
of the lens; in this case it's a F1.4 lens so that means capital F equals 1.4. The smaller
F值越大，镜头的聚光能力越强，图像越亮
the F-number the greater is the light gathering power of the lens, the brighter image that
它会创造。让我们简化一下，看看镜头是如何工作的。
it will create. Let's simplify things and see how lenses work.
我们在世界上有一个简单的物体，我们有一个镜头。并且镜头由a描述
We have a simple object in the world and we have a lens. And a lens is described by a
焦距，在这种情况下，我们有一个我们称之为薄透镜模型。这可能是
focal length and in this case we have what we call a thin lens model. This is probably
你对高中物理学很熟悉。相机中的真实镜头
familiar to you from high school physics. The real lenses that you have in your camera
不像这样的简单镜头，但它们可以用单个镜头近似。
are not simple lenses like this, but they can be approximated by a single lens.
透镜由两个焦点描述，每个焦点距离中心平面的距离为F.
The lens is described by two focal points, each a distance F away from the centre plane
镜头要查看对象图像的位置，我们执行此操作非常简单
of the lens. To see where the image of the object falls, we perform this very simple
几何和小箭头显示图像的形成位置。这是十字路口
geometry and the small arrow shows where the image will be formed. It's the intersection
两条黄线。这个图像形成过程在数学上非常简单地描述，
of the two yellow lines. This image formation process is described quite simply mathematically,
我们称之为“Zo”的物体的距离是形成图像的距离
the distance of the object which we call "Zo" the distance at which the image is formed
“Zi”在这里与此等式相关，所以Zi是距离中心的距离
"Zi" is related by this equation here, so Zi is the distance away from the centre of
镜头，将形成一个清晰的图像，这就是我们所说的“图像平面”。
the lens, where a sharp image will be formed and that's what we call the "Image Plane."
这就是图像形成的地方，也就是放置传感器的地方。现在传感器可能
That's where the image is formed and that's where we put the sensor. Now the sensor might
在过去一直是一部电影，今天我们更有可能放置
have been a piece of film in the old days, today it's much more likely that we place
半导体成像芯片;大量的光敏元件和输出
a semiconductor imaging chip; a large array of light sensitive elements and the output
这个阵列的数字记录，并放入手机或手机的闪存中
of this array is recorded digitally and placed into the flash memory in the phone or the
相机。
camera.
现在让我们来看看如果我将物体移近镜头会发生什么。该
Now let's look at what happens if I move the object a little bit closer to the lens. The
Zo的价值已经降低了，我们做了几何结构，我们现在看到了
value of Zo has been reduced and we do the geometric construction, we see now that the
图像形成于不同的地方;Zi具有不同的值，如等式​​所示
image is formed in a different place; Zi has got a different value, as given by the equation
在底部。这意味着如果我在原始位置有图像平面，
down the bottom. What this means is that if I had the image plane in the original location,
那里我会有一个模糊的图像;那个图像会失焦。
I would have a fuzzy image there; that image would be out of focus.
为了创建聚焦图像，我需要将图像平面移动到此处以及是否
In order to create a focussed image, I need to move the image plane over to here and if
我将图像平面放在那里，然后我会有一个清晰的物体图像。所以这个
I place the image plane there, then I will have a sharp image of my object. And so this
当我调整旧式相机的焦点时会发生什么。当我旋转
is what happens when I adjust the focus of an old fashioned type camera. As I rotate
镜头为了聚焦它，那里有一个螺纹实际上正在移动
the lens in order to focus it, there's a screw thread there which is actually moving the
镜头远离传感器或胶片的平面。所以为了聚焦相机，什么
lens away from the plane of the sensor or the film. So in order to focus a camera, what
我需要做的是改变镜头和图像所在平面之间的距离
I need to do is to change the distance between the lens and the plane where the image is
形成并捕获。
formed and captured.
这是一个动画，显示了这一点。当物体朝向镜头移动时，我们可以看到，
Here's an animation that shows this. As the object moves towards the lens, we can see,
只需使用简单的几何结构，图像的位置就会进一步移动
just using the simple geometric construction, that the location of the image is moving further
并且远离镜头，所以为了使它成为焦点，我需要移动镜头
and further away from the lens, so in order to bring it into focus, I need to move the
图像平面远离镜头。
image plane away from the lens.
有趣的是针孔相机不需要聚焦。无论距离如何
Interestingly a pinhole camera does not require focussing. Irrespective of the distance of
物体，它形成的图像总是很清晰，但针孔的缺点
the object, the image that it forms is always sharp, but the disadvantage of the pinhole
我之前提到过的镜头是，图像非常非常微弱。所以它不需要聚焦
lens as I mentioned earlier, is that the images are very, very faint. So it doesn't need focussing
但它不会产生明亮的图像。
but it doesn't produce bright images.